<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.tvtunes.ex" name="TvTunes Ex" version="100.5.8.007" provider-name="robwebset, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.2.1"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
		<provides>video</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib" />
	<extension point="kodi.context.item" library="contextmenu.py">
		<item>
			<label>32995</label>
			<visible>!String.IsEmpty(Window(home).Property(TvTunes_ShowContextMenu)) + [Container.Content(movies) | Container.Content(episodes) | Container.Content(tvshows) | Container.Content(seasons)]</visible>
		</item>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Retrieve and play your soundtrack or video themes whilst browsing your library</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Получить и воспроизвести музыкальную темы, просматривая вашу библиотеку</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Отримати та відтворити музичну теми, переглядаючи вашу бібліотеку</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">TvTunes is equipped with powerful features that enable the fetching, organising and playing of themes whilst browsing your Kodi library.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">TvTunes оснащен мощными функциями, которые позволяют извлекать, организовывать и воспроизводить темы во время просмотра вашей библиотеки Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">TvTunes оснащений потужними функціями, які дозволяють витягати, організовувати і відтворювати теми під час перегляду вашої бібліотеки Kodi.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">The collection of themes is maintain as a source to consult historical archives of music themes for movies and series. Thus its only purpose is educational and referential, and it is not maintained for the purpose of reselling and re-distributing music or for profitable purpose. Its access is intended strictly in the same way people access plots, trailers, scripts or other material in connection to a film. Any donation is with the purpose of supporting TvTunes' development and towards the costs of maintaining the library. Any holder of rights to these themes who would like to have their material removed from the archives just needs to request so by contacting TvTunes's Theme Library via the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Коллекция тем поддерживается в качестве источника для ознакомления с историческими архивами музыкальных тем для фильмов и сериалов. Таким образом, его единственная цель - образовательная и справочная, и она не поддерживается с целью перепродажи и перераспределения музыки или с выгодой. Его доступ предназначен точно так же, как люди получают доступ к сюжетам, трейлерам, сценариям или другим материалам в связи с фильмом. Любое пожертвование делается с целью поддержки развития TvTunes и расходов на содержание библиотеки. Любой обладатель прав на эти темы, кто хотел бы удалить свои материалы из архивов, должен просто запросить это, связавшись с библиотекой тем TvTunes через форум Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Колекція тем підтримується як джерело для ознайомлення з історичними архівами музичних тем для фільмів і серіалів. Таким чином, його єдина мета - освітня та довідкова, і вона не підтримується з метою перепродажу і перерозподілу музики або з вигодою. Його доступ призначений точно так же, як люди отримують доступ до сюжетів, трейлерам, сценаріями або інших матеріалів в зв'язку з фільмом. Будь-яке пожертвування робиться з метою підтримки розвитку TvTunes і витрат на утримання бібліотеки. Кожний власник прав на ці теми, хто хотів би видалити свої матеріали з архівів, повинен просто запросити це, зв'язавшись з бібліотекою тим TvTunes через форум Kodi.</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>See LICENSE.txt</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.tvtunes.ex.git</source>
		<news></news>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<banner>resources/banner.jpg</banner>
			<logo>resources/logo.png</logo>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
